onlinefabricstore.net 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy | OnlineFabricStore.net

### Last Updated: August 17, 2016

OnlineFabricStore.net is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. As a result, we will not disclose any contact information including email, telephone or address information that you provide to us on www.onlinefabricstore.net (the "Site"), to any third party except as described in this privacy policy (our "Privacy Policy"). 

### Web Orders and SSL Security

All personal information submitted when placing an order on this web Site is secured using industry standard 128-bit encryption, which is provided by our SSL (secure sockets layer) certificate. When checking out, the shopping cart system will automatically redirect to the secure section of this Site. During checkout, you will see a small lock icon (icon's location varies by browser) in your browser. This icon verifies that your transaction is secure.

* * *

### Promotional Mailings

On occasion, we may contact you with news, coupons or promotions via email or regular mail, if you have previously signed up for such mailings. If, at any time, you wish to opt-out of these mailings, simply click on the unsubscribe link that can be found at the bottom of every promotional email. Or you can send an email to [help@onlinefabricstore.net](mailto:help@onlinefabricstore.net) with "remove" in the title, and your name will be removed from our list within 48 hours. You can also unsubscribe by sending us a notice at the regular address listed below.

* * *

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Statement at any time. If we change this Statement, this Site will be updated. Each time you visit the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement as they are in effect at the time. Please be sure to check this Statement often so you will always be aware of the steps taken concerning your personal information.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, want to request "do not share/do not send" status, or otherwise need to contact us concerning this Statement, please contact our customer service. 

* * *

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our Site or place an order.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our Site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

* * *

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To process transactions.
  * To send you information about specials and promotions that we may be having on our Site.
  * To enhance our Site to provide better service and functionality to our customers.

* * *

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

* * *

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a Site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the Sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

* * *

###  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. However, we do share our your information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses, including analyzing the use of the Site to make it a better shopping environment.

* * *

### Your Choices

If you prefer not to receive communications from us, regarding special offers, products, or promotions, please email us at [help@onlinefabricstore.net](mailto:help@onlinefabricstore.net). Information on how to opt out of receiving marketing email is provided in every email, or you may email us, or you may write us at www.onlinefabricstore.net, PO Box 1051, West Springfield, MA 01090. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, and specifically what type of information you do not want to receive. If you opt out of receiving marketing email, we will continue to send you emails regarding order confirmation and shipment notification when you place an order with us. 

* * *

###  Changing Information

To update your customer information, please log in to the My Account section of the Site, email us at [help@onlinefabricstore.net](mailto:help@onlinefabricstore.net) or contact us at www.onlinefabricstore.net, PO Box 1051, West Springfield, MA 01090. You can direct us to remove your name from our lists by following the instructions in Your Choices above. For your security you may be asked to provide certain information to identify yourself before we will accept changes to your information. If we receive a request from a third party regarding, or requesting a change in, use of your customer information, we reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to not grant the request from such third party (unless required to do so by law) and/or to require that you personally confirm the third party request. 

* * *

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page or by contacting us at the address listed below.

* * *

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Site is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under 13 years of age, do not use our Site.

* * *

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Site and not to information collected offline.

* * *

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site at https://www.onlinefabricstore.net/terms.aspx.

* * *

### Your Consent

By using our Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

* * *

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date above. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

* * *

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

* * *

### Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our Privacy Policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commission Fair Information Practices  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

Respectfully,

OnlineFabricStore.net
